const questions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What's the Nine Tail's name?",
        options: [
            "Gyuuki",
            "Kurama",
            "Choumei",
            "Kyuubi"
        ],
        answer: "Kurama",
        explanation: "Kurama is the true name of the Nine-Tails Fox, a powerful Tailed Beast."
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "What was Obito/Madara's ultimate plan called?",
        options: [
            "Tsuki no Sekai",
            "Tsuki no Keikaku",
            "Tsuki no Me Keikaku",
            "Infinite Tsukuyomi"
        ],
        answer: 'Tsuki no Me Keikaku',
        explanation: "Infinite Tsukuyomi is the name of the jutsu while Tsuki no mi is the name of Obito’s project  Tsuki means moon 'me' means eye  so its called Eye of Moon"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "What is the name of Zabuza's sword?",
        options: [
            "Kubikiribocho",
            "Samehada",
            "Kabutowari",
            "Hakarihada"
        ],
        answer: 'Kubikiribocho',
        explanation: "Zabuza wielded Kubikiribocho, known for its ability to regenerate by absorbing blood."
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "How many times did Naruto fail the graduation test from the Academy?",
        options: [
            "Once",
            "Four times",
            "Twice",
            "Three times"
        ],
        answer: "Three times",
        explanation: "Naruto failed the graduation test three times before finally passing."
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "What is the name given to the leader of the Water Village?",
        options: [
            "Raikage",
            "Hoshikage",
            "Tsuchikage",
            "Mizukage"
        ],
        answer: "Mizukage",
        explanation: "The leader of the Hidden Mist Village (Kirigakure) is called the Mizukage."
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "Who of these below has Kekkei Tōta?",
        options: [
            "Hiruzen",
            "Madara",
            "Ōnoki",
            "Kakashi"
        ],
        answer: "Ōnoki",
        explanation: "Ōnoki possesses a Kekkei Tōta, which allows him to use the Dust Release technique."
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Who was the main character in Jiraiya's first book — The Tale of the Utterly Gutsy Shinobi?",
        options: [
            "Naruto", 
            "Nagato",
            "Minato",
            "Yahiko"
        ],
        answer: "Naruto",
        explanation: "The main character in Jiraiya's book was inspired by Naruto Uzumaki."
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "What was Kakashi's father called?",
        options: [
            "White Dog",
            "White Fang",
            "White Lion",
            "White Bird"
        ],
        answer: "White Fang",
        explanation: "Kakashi's father was known as the White Fang of Konoha, a legendary shinobi."
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "Who told Naruto he could graduate if he stole the Forbidden Scroll?",
        options: [
            "Kakashi",
            "Iruka",
            "Orochimaru",
            "Mizuki"
        ],
        answer: "Mizuki",
        explanation: "Mizuki deceived Naruto into stealing the Forbidden Scroll by promising him graduation."
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "What is the name of Itachi's first partner at Akatsuki?",
        options: [
            "Jūzō Biwa",
            "Kisame Hoshigaki",
            "Orochimaru",
            "Deidara"
        ],
        answer: 'Jūzō Biwa',
        explanation: "Itachi Uchiha's first partner in the Akatsuki was Jūzō Biwa. Jūzō, a member of the infamous Seven Ninja Swordsmen of the Mist, was known for wielding the sword Kubikiribōchō."
    }
];
